thank you
ICICI longboard launches a flee of 14
new products across Health motor and
Cooperative segments the comprehensive
lineup of initiative and Tech enabled
Insurance offerings will revolutionize
customer experience Bangalore 22nd
February 2023 ICICI Lombard India's
leading private non-life insurance
company launched its latest lineup of 14
new or enhanced Insurance Solutions
including Riders add-ons and upgrade
across Health motor travel and
Cooperative segments the flue of
offering announced at a press conference
in Bengaluru on Wednesday offers a
comprehensive array of product across
categories for a wide spectrum of
customers the products suit shall
transform the way consumers experience
in insurance
providing them the seamless journey and
Tech enhanced Solutions
with the single Insurance Company
so there wouldn't be any hassle during
the renewal because today most of the
vehicles like what we see is
uninsured vehicles are more on the road
so with this what will happen
okay we will be considering those
Vehicles so if you run away if something
happens to those Vehicles those vehicles
are covered so under uh Isis remember
family truth okay we ensure that all the
vehicles which are that are getting
ensured so with this what will happen is
it would be like one policy
foreign
policies
and then next is pair as you use
during the long term especially like
during long-term internet
people used to renew the policies but
they were not using it
okay whether you use the vehicle you
don't use the rental premium used to be
the same okay and even
also now presently most of uh the
corporates still work from home is going
on okay so during during the present
scenario also there are many corporate
customers where they tell that I will
try only this many kilometers why I
should pay sale for the person who is
Driving unlimited
with this cover we can restrict our work
coverages like there are multiple plans
5000 kilometers or 7 500 10 000 and
about ten thousand customer can opt and
he will be charged only for the
kilometer what he drives
so it is paid
as you use
[Music]
today like uh within the family or
within ourselves like one sir will be
driving this car very nicely okay he'll
maintain his car okay while timing he
will not do any excessive breaking over
speeding but I as an individual might be
I'll be trying very largely so with the
telematic device what we do is we
monitor almost around eight to ten
parameters through telematic device we
monitor the usage Behavior he uh
what what kind of a speed he is doing
okay and distance what he is traveling
with all those okay a score has been
captured at the end of the year based on
that the discount is passed to the
customer because a corporate a doctor
what uh initially when I told doctor
would be driving for minimal kilometers
but as a builder or a construction
company if someone is using it for his
business purpose he'll be driving more
so the premium difference earlier the
premium used to be seen for doctor and
other also but now with this there would
be difference in feeding
where with this coverage is what we
cover is uh accidental hospitalization
where we reimburse up to 10 lakh Rupees
okay for everyone including the
occupants
who all are involved in the accident
including the output and Max solution
okay hospitalization uh reimbursement
can be done and we have the ambulance
cover also where the maximum
submentation is up to two lakh and
Hospital daily cash
we have that thousand rupees per day we
give so if what it happens if somebody
is there in the hospital for seven days
so
first two days okay it was for medical
checkup and everything so after that
whatever it is up to 10 days we covered
and then we have a tele consultation
where up to five consultation what
initially even without told in a license
app also it is there so similar to that
we have Telegraph circulation
foreign
[Music]
Diagnostics
hospitals
foreign
[Music]
home insurance
foreign